<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Go Go Academy</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Free Online Courses</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 08:11:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.5.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/cropped-16X16-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Go Go Academy</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Fiverr Marketing: Freelance To Start Your Online Business.[Free Download]</title>
		<link>/38/</link>
					<comments>/38/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 08:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Freelance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=38</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Register and Create Your First Fiverr Account. How to Success Hack Fiverr&#8217;s Top Sellers to Ensure More Sales. How to Optimize Your Fiverr Gigs for More Traffic and Sales. How to Find and Keep Good Fiverr Customers. Fiverr No No&#8217;s. How to Avoid Negative Feedback on Fiverr. How to Get Your First Reviews on Fiverr. [&#8230;] <a class="g1-link g1-link-more" href="/38/">More</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul><li>Register and Create Your First Fiverr Account.</li><li>How to Success Hack Fiverr&#8217;s Top Sellers to Ensure More Sales.</li><li>How to Optimize Your Fiverr Gigs for More Traffic and Sales.</li><li>How to Find and Keep Good Fiverr Customers.</li><li>Fiverr No No&#8217;s.</li><li>How to Avoid Negative Feedback on Fiverr.</li><li>How to Get Your First Reviews on Fiverr.</li><li>Know How to Research and Find The Best-Selling Fiverr Gigs.</li><li>How to Create Fiverr Gigs Like a Pro!</li><li>How to Make Money on Fiverr Even If You Don&#8217;t Have Any Skills!</li><li>How to Deliver Like Fiverr Top Sellers Do.</li><li>How to Use Fiverr Gig Extras and Packages.</li><li>How to Get More Sales on Fiverr.</li><li>Insider Top Seller Secrets to Making More Money on Fiverr.</li></ul>



<p></p>



<p>What Are You Waiting For?</p>



<p>See You Inside!!!</p>



<p>+SEE UDEMY 129.99$ COURSE : <strong><a href="https://www.udemy.com/course/fiverr-marketing-freelance-and-start-your-online-business/" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.udemy.com/course/fiverr-marketing-freelance-and-start-your-online-business/">LINK</a></strong></p>



<p><strong>-To be sure that you will be not lazy during consuming the course I need you to signup on fiver first and send me your username on messenger to know that you are serious about working online and making $$$ only then I will send you the paid course for free immediately :</strong></p>



<p>+FIVERR SIGNUP :&nbsp;<strong><a href="https://track.fiverr.com/visit/?bta=158112&amp;brand=fiverrcpa">CLICK HERE</a></strong></p>



<p>+TALK TO ME ON MESSANGER :&nbsp;<strong><a href="https://m.me/115888026942204" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CLICK HERE</a></strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/38/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fiverr: How To Start Freelancing Career With Fiverr.[Free Download]</title>
		<link>/31/</link>
					<comments>/31/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 07:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Freelance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=31</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fiverr has become the &#8216;go to&#8217; freelance service destination on the internet Given its low cost profile compared to other free form or custom order freelance resources, Fiverr stands to continue to attract a lot of buyer attention. Compared to traditional freelancing, Fiverr removes a lot of doubt and guesswork from the freelance process. But [&#8230;] <a class="g1-link g1-link-more" href="/31/">More</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Fiverr has become the &#8216;go to&#8217; freelance service destination on the internet</strong></p>



<p>Given its low cost profile compared to other free form or custom order freelance resources, Fiverr stands to continue to attract a lot of buyer attention.</p>



<p>Compared to traditional freelancing, Fiverr removes a lot of doubt and guesswork from the freelance process.</p>



<p>But if you don&#8217;t know what you&#8217;re doing or if you don&#8217;t have a strategy, you end up wasting time and money, in the form of opportunity costs.</p>



<p><strong>With this video course you will learn the best strategies for making</strong><strong>your full-time income on Fiverr.</strong></p>



<p><strong>Topics covered:</strong></p>



<ul><li>Fiverr&#8217;s Secrets</li><li>The Good News?</li><li>The Biggest Hassle With Fiverr</li><li>6 Better Ways To Make Money Off Fiverr</li><li>Offer Premium Value-added Services</li><li>Bundle Other&#8217;s Services and Sell Turnkey Assets</li><li>Bundle Other&#8217;s Services and Sell Operational Assets</li><li>Buy Services That Help You Buy Resell able High-value Assets</li><li>Resell Cheap Fiverr Services at Other High Value Location</li><li>Resell Cheap Fiverr Services at Other High Value Location</li></ul>



<p>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;What You Will Get</p>



<ul><li><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.0/72x72/2714.png" alt="✔" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Lifetime Access to All Future Facebook Messenger Bot Updates<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.0/72x72/2714.png" alt="✔" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Fast &amp; Friendly Support in the Q&amp;A section<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.0/72x72/2714.png" alt="✔" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Udemy Certificate of Completion Ready for Download<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.0/72x72/2714.png" alt="✔" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> A 30 Day &#8220;No Questions Asked&#8221; Money Back Guarantee! This offer won&#8217;t last forever. If you want to take your business to the next level, then this is the course for you!<br><strong>&#8220;Take This Course&#8221; to Start Freelancing &amp; Become a Top Rated Fiverr Seller</strong></li></ul>



<p></p>



<p>What Are You Waiting For?</p>



<p>See You Inside!!!</p>



<p>+SEE UDEMY 129.99$ COURSE : <strong><a href="https://www.udemy.com/course/fiverr-start-freelancing-become-a-top-rated-fiverr-seller-on-fiverr/?couponCode=STAYHOME" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.udemy.com/course/fiverr-start-freelancing-become-a-top-rated-fiverr-seller-on-fiverr/?couponCode=STAYHOME">LINK</a></strong></p>



<p><strong>-To be sure that you will be not lazy during consuming the course I need you to signup on fiver first and send me your username on messenger to know that you are serious about working online and making $$$ only then I will send you the paid course for free immediately :</strong></p>



<p>+FIVERR SIGNUP :&nbsp;<strong><a href="https://track.fiverr.com/visit/?bta=158112&amp;brand=fiverrcpa">CLICK HERE</a></strong></p>



<p>+TALK TO ME ON MESSANGER :&nbsp;<strong><a href="https://m.me/115888026942204" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CLICK HERE</a></strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/31/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Complete Freelancing Course-Upwork Fiverr Home Business. [Free Download]</title>
		<link>/26/</link>
					<comments>/26/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 07:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Freelance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=26</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Freelancing&#160;done right creates the ultimate in employment and career stability. You can be your own boss. And you can be a well-paid&#160;freelancer with full benefits, IF you build your freelancing business right. From the ground up. It doesn&#8217;t matter whether you are creating or running a&#160;copywriting business&#160;or a&#160;web design business. It doesn&#8217;t matter if you [&#8230;] <a class="g1-link g1-link-more" href="/26/">More</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p></p>



<p><strong>Freelancing</strong>&nbsp;done right creates the ultimate in employment and career stability. You can be your own boss. And you can be a well-paid&nbsp;<strong>freelancer with full benefits</strong>, IF you build your freelancing business right. From the ground up.</p>



<p>It doesn&#8217;t matter whether you are creating or running a&nbsp;<strong>copywriting business</strong>&nbsp;or a&nbsp;<strong>web design business</strong>. It doesn&#8217;t matter if you are a&nbsp;<strong>home business</strong>&nbsp;or on the road constantly. If you want a&nbsp;<strong>successful freelancing career,</strong>&nbsp;you must follow core business fundamentals that position&nbsp; you to soar! This course will teach you how.</p>



<p>Being&nbsp;<strong>a successful freelancer</strong>&nbsp;in today&#8217;s gig economy isn&#8217;t just about having slick<strong>&nbsp;copywriting for your o</strong><strong>ffer on Fiverr and Upwork&nbsp;</strong>(though that isn&#8217;t a bad start), it is about a long-term positioning and strategy that allows you to build financial as well as intellectual capital.</p>



<p>To some,&nbsp;<strong>freelancing&nbsp;</strong>means instability and low wages. To you, after taking this course,&nbsp;<strong>freelancing</strong>&nbsp;will mean high income, career stability, industry influence, and the power to call your own shots.</p>



<p>This course will teach you how to establish a strong foundation for&nbsp;<strong>your freelancing caree</strong>r so that you can continually grow, increase fees, attract better customers and clients, and command respect from all you deal with.&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;</p>



<p>Whether you are an accidental<strong>&nbsp;freelancer</strong>&nbsp;or one entering the field on purpose, this course will provide you with shortcuts to success. Nothing good happens overnight, but you don&#8217;t have to go through a multi-year, trial-and-error process before coming up with a system that works for you and your lifestyle.&nbsp; &nbsp;</p>



<p>Freelancing done poorly can make you end up feeling like an over-tired, stressed, impoverished indentured servant. Freelancing done the right way can give you a lifestyle of creative and professional control coupled with financial freedom.&nbsp; &nbsp;</p>



<p>Message from the instructor</p>



<p><em>&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &#8220;I&#8217;ve been a full-time freelancer for the last 25 years. The freelancing existence has led to the lifestyle of my dreams. I&#8217;ve traveled the&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;world, worked from home, been paid handsomely and generated profits that paid for all I could ever want. It wasn&#8217;t easy at first, but I can</em><em>teach you the fastest way to position yourself for both short-term long-term success.&#8221; TJ Walker</em></p>



<p>You can get clients to call you and ask for your availability</p>



<p>You can get clients to realize the full value of your experience and expertise</p>



<p>You can give yourself a raise every year.</p>



<p>You can give yourself full benefits</p>



<p>You can give yourself vacations</p>



<p>You can create long-term economic stability without fear of ever getting fired.</p>



<p>What Are You Waiting For?</p>



<p>See You Inside!!!</p>



<p>+SEE UDEMY 129.99$ COURSE : <strong><a href="https://www.udemy.com/course/the-complete-freelancing-course-upwork-fiverr-home-business/?couponCode=2D29749C7E679C32D191" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.udemy.com/course/the-complete-freelancing-course-upwork-fiverr-home-business/?couponCode=2D29749C7E679C32D191">LINK</a></strong></p>



<p><strong>-To be sure that you will be not lazy during consuming the course I need you to signup on fiver first and send me your username on messenger to know that you are serious about working online and making $$$ only then I will send you the paid course for free immediately :</strong></p>



<p>+FIVERR SIGNUP :&nbsp;<strong><a href="https://track.fiverr.com/visit/?bta=158112&amp;brand=fiverrcpa">CLICK HERE</a></strong></p>



<p>+TALK TO ME ON MESSANGER :&nbsp;<strong><a href="https://m.me/115888026942204" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CLICK HERE</a></strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/26/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fiverr Empire: Kickstart a Fiverr Career &#038; Fiverr Brokering. [Free Download]</title>
		<link>/5/</link>
					<comments>/5/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 01:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Freelance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=5</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Turn Your Skills and Talents into Profitable Business Have you ever had the sudden thought to quit whatever you’re doing now? Feeling tired and bored with your current 9 to 5 conventional job? Sitting on the same old desk for 5 to 10 years, working on the same routine day by day, Being underappreciated by [&#8230;] <a class="g1-link g1-link-more" href="/5/">More</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p></p>



<p><strong>Turn Your Skills and Talents into Profitable Business</strong></p>



<p>Have you ever had the sudden thought to quit whatever you’re doing now?</p>



<p>Feeling tired and bored with your current 9 to 5 conventional job?</p>



<p>Sitting on the same old desk for 5 to 10 years, working on the same routine day by day, Being underappreciated by your boss and paid peanuts for a pile of tasks you have done.</p>



<p>Most importantly, you lost your direction and passion. You’re not doing something you like for life. You lack a platform to show your skills and talents.</p>



<p>Working is a lifetime event. If working life is torturing, you’re not going to be happy with it for the rest of your life too. Instead of doing something that you hate, why not working on somethingyou are truly passionate?</p>



<p>How about starting your independent career on a platform where you can make use of your skills and talents to earn top dollars in a wealthy and profitable way?</p>



<p>The platform We are going to introduce you is&nbsp;<strong>Fiverr</strong>.</p>



<p><strong>What is Fiverr anyway? And how can you achieve Fiverr success for beginners? What is Fiverr Arbitrage?</strong></p>



<p>If you’re an active netizen, I am sure you’ve heard of Fiverr and Fiverr gigs. In case you don’t, Fiverr is a platform where you could post a freelancing offer of your service, and anyone else from the world that needs your service will pay you to do it, it is called Fiverr gigs. You don’t have to attend to an office. Instead, you could just work at the comfort of your home.<br>&lt;br&gt;As long as you have a digital device that can access the internet. Of course, most importantly, you must have internet or Wifi. Besides, you could also work on a flexible basis at times whenever you’re convenient. Every job you offer at Fiverr starts at a flat rate of $5 gig.</p>



<p>Until today, there are already a few millions of freelancers using Fiverr to make extra income. Some of them have even quit their full-time job, to focus on building their online &#8220;Fiverr&#8221; career entirely. If you’re looking for a breakthrough in your career, this is it.</p>



<p><strong>Opening the door to Fiverr Giggs Empire</strong></p>



<p>Feeling frustrated with your working life? Today, you can put a halt on it. I am opening my door to Fiverr Blueprint where you can extract everything in my course and start your independent career and achieve Fiverr success as soon as today!</p>



<p><strong>The Top Benefits You Can Gain From Our Blueprint and Start Your Career At Fiverr and Fiverr gigs Today</strong></p>



<ul><li>Flexible Working Hours</li></ul>



<p>You don’t have a fixed schedule to follow, as long as you can complete your job within the promised timeline. You can work whenever you like!</p>



<ul><li>Work At The Comfort Of Your Home</li></ul>



<p>Working in pyjama on your cozy bed is your dream career? Now you could do it from the comfort of your home or even cafe. Wherever you desire!</p>



<ul><li>Extra Income Stream</li></ul>



<p>If you’re using Fiverr as a part-time job, you could earn extra income besides getting paid from your full-time job. Extra income could allow you to have more fancy meals!</p>



<ul><li>Show Off The Talents You Possess</li></ul>



<p>Are your talents appreciated by your boss? Don’t let him/her define your capability. There are millions of customers who know how to appreciate your talents and pay you doing it</p>



<ul><li>Sharpen Your Skills</li></ul>



<p>Have a drawing gift? But your full-time job is downgrading your skill? You could now regain your skills by offering services at Fiverr gigs and start to sharpen your skills even more!</p>



<ul><li>To Achieve Financial Freedom</li></ul>



<p>There are millions of users having an independent career at Fiverr. Their success has made them achieve financial freedom because Fiverr is a profitable platform!</p>



<p>That&#8217;s Not All!!!</p>



<p>Without Performing The Gigs Yourself, You Can Pocket More Than 5K A Month By Outsourcing The Gigs! That is Fiverr Arbitrage.</p>



<p>The Only Job You Have Is Looking For More Customers and Keeping The Difference Profits. In The Boss Way.</p>



<p>If you were going to ask us ways to make money online, We are going to tell you that the potential of the internet has no boundary. There are tons of ways to make money online. The only questionable problem is – how much you can make.</p>



<p>Will you be surprised that the average income of start-ups is just $1000 or below every month?</p>



<p>Most of the internet marketers are struggling since the first day they started. This is because they don’t have a proper lesson and training course to follow. Undeniably Google is the know-it-all, but if everything from Googleis applicable, I guess the failure rate will be much lower. But that’s not the case, unfortunately.</p>



<p>Fiverr has become a favorite platform for freelancers to kick-start their first online business empire. By offering their services based on their expertise to earn extra income or as a full-time job. Moreover, it is also to believe that millions of Fiverr freelancers have successfully made more than 10K per month.</p>



<p>Contradictory, there is also a group of people who are performing at a mediocre level. For not be able to make even 1K per month. This doesn’t imply that Fiverr is not a good platform to start. What you need to be given is a professional training course.</p>



<p>Stop Figuring Out Your Own, Start Your Fiverr Business Now With Fiverr Empire Brokering Secrets. Wewill lead you to achieve Fiverr success for beginners.</p>



<p>What do you do when you’re stuck in the middle of the road? You figure a way out on your own. But figuring out on your own is tiring and time-consuming. What you need is an instant solution. Something that allows you to see results almost instantly.</p>



<p>Today, all your confusion and problems will be solved. I have come out with a blueprint called Fiverr Brokering Secrets.</p>



<p>Our blueprint will give you a step-by-step guide to how you can become a Fiverr Broker to allocate more time looking for freelancers and customers instead of performing the gigs yourself. Fiverr Arbitrage will leverage your business and generate more profits. Simply put, you’re a boss where you hire freelancers to work for you at the same time you charge from your clients.</p>



<p><strong>Let&#8217;s Do Some Maths.<br></strong></p>



<p>By acing Fiverr Arbitrage, your hourly wages have just levelled up to $30.<br>Guess not even your conventional 9-5 job can pay you such a high rate.</p>



<p>Let’s assume that you only work for 6 hours a day.</p>



<p>Your daily income will become $180. (Without doing any Fiverr gigs!)</p>



<p>There are 30 days in a month, which means your monthly income would be $5400!</p>



<p>Remember, all you do is just outsourcing and looking for customers. You don’t perform the Fiverr gigs yourself.</p>



<p>Besides, working online enables you to work at the comfort of your home which makes your life more flexible than having a full-time job.</p>



<p>Do you think $5400 is the only amount you make? Definitely no! $5400 is just a beginner’s level income! As time goes by and more customers are getting to know you, your business quota will increase over time. Thus, you will make more profits than you first started.</p>



<p>What Are You Waiting For?</p>



<p>See You Inside!!!</p>



<p>+SEE UDEMY 129$ COURSE : <strong><a href="https://www.udemy.com/course/fiverr-empire-kickstart-a-fiverr-career-fiverr-brokering/" data-type="URL" data-id="https://www.udemy.com/course/fiverr-empire-kickstart-a-fiverr-career-fiverr-brokering/">LINK</a> </strong></p>



<p><strong>-To be sure that you will be not lazy during consuming the course I need you to signup on fiver first and send me your username on messenger to know that you are serious about working online and making $$$ only then I will send you the paid course for free immediately :</strong></p>



<p>+FIVERR SIGNUP :  <strong><a href="https://track.fiverr.com/visit/?bta=158112&amp;brand=fiverrcpa" data-type="URL" data-id="https://track.fiverr.com/visit/?bta=158112&amp;brand=fiverrcpa">CLICK HERE</a></strong></p>



<p>+TALK TO ME ON MESSANGER : <strong><a href="https://m.me/115888026942204" data-type="URL" data-id="https://m.me/115888026942204" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CLICK HERE</a></strong></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/5/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 37/44 objects using apc
Page Caching using apc (Page is feed) 
Database Caching using apc

Served from: dailyrewards04.06-3.com @ 2020-09-28 08:22:43 by W3 Total Cache
-->